excitel.com 2018-07-12

# Privacy Policy | Your Personal Information is Safe with Excitel

This policy covers the way Excitel Broadband Pvt. Ltd. treats personal information that the Company receives and collects, including information related to Customer’s past use of the Company’s products and services. Personal information means information about Customers which identifies them like Customer’s name, address, e-mail address, phone number etc.

### Collection and General Use of Personal Information

The Company collects personal information when customer registers for the purpose of using Company’s products , when the  Customer registers for visit the Company web pages or the pages of certain partners of the Company. The Company may  mutually use personal information that is  obtained from business partners or other Companies. The Company has the right to deliver the Customer’s information  to its business associates, franchisees without referring the same to the Customer.

When the Customer registers with the Company, the Company receives information about the  Customer’s  name, telephone number, e-mail address, P.O. address, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, and personal interests and any other ID related to the specific service Customer applies for. When the Customer registers with the Company and sign in to Company’s services,  the Customer acquires a status of  valued one. The Company collects information about  Customer’s  transactions with the Company and its business partners included. Information is collected about  Customer’s use of the demanded products. The Company can use this  information to  customize its products. The same includes anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

### Sharing and Disclosure of Personal Information

The Company does not share personal information about the Customer with other parties.

### Changes of Privacy Policy

The Company may update this policy and display the same in its website without notice to the Customer and such posting will be deemed to have been read by the the Customer.
